Almost. Almost. There you go.
He was that thorough. Well, can you recover anything?
Yeah, I can wait.
Who does the number belong to?
Her name's Liu Lan. She lived at 48 Tongli Lane in the Nandu District.
Come on. You're right there. That's it?
Weird thing is, records show she passed away a few years ago.
Are you sure?
Why would the text from Xu Shan Shan's phone go to the number of a dead woman?
Sir, you're going to have to wait on that. We've got a situation down here.
Wait, what? And they said they're a witness?
All right, then. Why don't you tell us everything from the beginning?
You're doing it wrong. Here, let me help.
You're listening to Xuسم market.
I've got to wait.
Be really.
I've got to wait for it.
Have to wait for you to see you in your run.
Turn in.
кто you and my friend of mine and my friend of mine is,
You know what?
The past story there, it's the wrong thing.